Guide to the Duke University Archives Photographic Negative Collection, 1855-1995
University Archives Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- Faculty Negatives
  - Faculty - B
    - Brodie, Chancellor, 1985 February
    - Brodie, Chancellor and Visiting Chancellors, 1982 November
    - Brodie, Dr. Keith, 1976 October
    - Bronfenbrenner, Dr. Martin, economics, 1971 March
    - Bronfenbrenner, Martin, economics, 1977 July 7
    - Bronfenbrenner, 1984 April
    - Brower receiving hospital award, 1956 January
    - Brown, Anne, nursing, 1975 November
    - Brown, Dr. B., 1961 May
    - Brown, Bobie, 1980 June
    - Brown, Charlotte and husband, 1977
    - Brown, Charlotte, 1975 September
    - Brown, Earl, 1960 May
    - Brown, Francis, 1962 February
    - Brown, Francis, passports, 1964 July
    - Brown, Harry E., 1960 February
    - Brown, Joshua, 1950 April 9
    - Brown, R. G., 1961 May
    - Brown, T., 1980 October
    - Brown, W. G., 1954 March
    - Brown, Wes, 1983 February
    - Brown, Wes, 1981 September
    - Brown, Susan
    - Browning, Robert, 1968 October
    - Brummett, Paul, 1983 October
    - Bryan, Anne-Marie, 1967 September
    - Bryan, Paul, 1976 September
    - Bryan, Mrs. Virginia, 1965 June
    - Buckley, Dr., grant presentation, 1968 June
    - Buckley, Dr., 1979 June 25
    - Buckley, Dr. Rebecca, in lab, 1967 May
    - Budd, Lewis/Louis, 1982 October
    - Budd, Lewis/Louis, English dept., 1975 March
    - Buehler, Al, athletic dept., 1955 September
    - Buehler, Al, passports, 1978 January
    - Bugg, Dr. Everett J., Jr., 1956 January
    - Bundick, Donald, 1963 March
    - Burian, Peter, passport
    - Burke, Father, 1981 June
    - Burke, Marian, 1980 August
    - Burney, dining halls, 1962 August
    - Burns, William, 1974 November
    - Burton, Col. Donovan, 1967 June
    - Burton, Rich, 1980 November
    - Busey
    - Bush, William, 1960 January
    - Business office personnel: Dozier, Henrichsen, Harward, 1963
    - Busse, Dr., 1972 April
    - Busse, Dr., in office, 1963
    - Butler, Joe, 1963 September
    - Butler, Joe, retired faculty, 1985 April
    - Butters, Ron, 1983 November
    - Butters, Ronald, 1973 July
    - Butters, Tom, 1973 March
    - Byers, Ralph, 1977 June
    - Byers, Ralph, office of the President, 1977 April
    - Byrne, Dr., lab, 1960 May
  - Faculty - C
    - Cady, Edwin H., 1977 October
    - Cady, Edwin, 1973 October
    - Caffrey, William, 1974 May
    - Cahow, Clark, passports, 1978 May
    - Cahow, Mrs. Clark, passports, 1978 May
    - Cahow, Clark and family, passports, 1972
    - Cahow, Clark, 1967 March
    - Calloway/Callaway making rounds, 1959 July
    - Calloway/Callaway, Dr., 1970 November
    - Campbell, Jerry, university librarian, 1985 July
    - Campbell, Mary B., 1968 May
    - Campbell, S. G., math, 1955 October
    - Cantor, M., passports, 1976 May
    - Capp, H., 1976 March
    - Carathers, Milton, chaplain, 1972 July
    - Carbone, Peter, 1967 October
    - Carden, Dr. Terrance, 1971 September
    - Carlson, Cathy, 1972 August
    - Carlite, Dr., JB Duke Professor, 1964 February
    - Carson, Robert C., 1963 March
    - Carter, B., 1970 September
    - Carter, Dr. Bayard, portrait
    - Carter, Dr. Bayard, portrait, 1955 October
    - Carter, Reginald D., 1980 July
    - Carter, Reginald, 1978 May
    - Cartwright and certificate feature, 1968 June
    - Casey, Ed, 1979 August
    - Casey, Craig H., Jr., 1981 May
    - Cassaboon, John, 1981 June
    - Cavanagh
    - Cavilito, Ann, 1986 January
    - Cell, John W., 1970 July
    - Cell, Mrs. John, passport, 1970 July
    - Chaddock, Jack, 1981 April
    - Chafe, William, 1980 October
    - Chafe, William H., 1986 December
    - Chaiken, Leon, 1954 May
    - Charlesworth, Dr. James, 1978 June
    - Charlesworth, James, 1973 July
    - Charlesworth, James, 1969 August
    - Charlesworth, James, religion dept., 1977 February
    - Chartier, Ken, soccer coach, 1982 February
    - Chase, Beatrice, 1982 April
    - Chavis, K. Z., 1968 March
    - Cheatham, passports
    - Chesnut, D. B., 1965 September
    - Chiorazzi, Mike, 1982
    - Christakos, Dr. Arthur, 1967 April
    - Christakos, Art, 1982 April
    - Christakos, Dr., 1964 February
    - Christian, C. D., 1965 October
  - Faculty - C (cont'd) (Box 32)
    - Christie, Dr., visa photo, 1978 September
    - Christie, Cathy, 1983
    - Christie, George, 1983 September
    - Christie, George C., law, 1974 March
    - Christie, George, passports, 1984 June
    - Christensen, Norm, botany dept., 1985 March
    - Christensen, Norman, botany dept., 1977 June
    - Ciompi, Giorgio, visiting artist, 1964 September
    - Cissy, 1980 June
    - Clark, Dr. Stephen, with Dr. Davison, 1943 November
    - Clark, Elon, Christmas cards, 1958 December
    - Clark, Howard, 1969 April
    - Clark, Dr. Howard, 1984 October
    - Clausen, Joy, passport, 1981 February
    - Clausen, Dr., 1965 March
    - Cleary, Walt, 1972 June
    - Cleaveland, provost, 1974 May
    - Cleland, Dean, 1965 November
    - Cleland, 1961 May
    - Cleland
    - Cleland by fireside, 1955 October
    - Cleland portrait
    - Cleland, Dean and Mrs. Jackson, 1964 November
    - Cleland, 1954 December
    - Cleland, Dr. and Mrs., passports, 1965 May
    - Cleland, Cannon and Anderson, 1957 September
    - Clotfelter, Charles, 1985 January
    - Clotfelter, Charles, 1983 May
    - Clotfelter, Charles, 1982
    - Clum, John, 1985 April
    - Clum, John, 1975 September
    - Clyde, Paul, honorary dinner for, 1961
    - Cobb, Claude, Jr.
    - Cocks, Frank, engineer, 1973 May
    - Cohen, Harvey J., 1982 April
    - Cohen, Kalman, 1984 April
    - Cohen, J. Kalman, management sciences, 1976 December
    - Cohen, J. Kalman, passports, 1975 January
    - Coker, Dr., 1970 June
    - Colby, Jack, passport, 1978 July
    - Cole, Taylor, reception, 1968 December
    - Cole, Taylor, 1983 January
    - Collier, David, business administration, 1980 September
    - Collins, Tom, 1986 July
    - Colton, Joel, 1985 March
    - Colton, Joel, passport, 1985 February
    - Colton, Joel, 1967 November
    - Connery, Frank, forestry, 1977 May
    - Conrad, Robert, 1984 April
    - Conrad family passports, 1981 March 22
    - Contanch, Patricia, M.D., 1982 January
    - Cook, Philip, 1985 August
    - Cook, Philip, 1981 April
    - Corbin, C., 1969 October
    - Corbin, C., passport, 1963 April
    - Corbin, C., retiring, 1977 December
    - Cordle, T. H., 1955 April
    - Corliss, Roger J., 1983 October
    - Corry, R. A., 1974
    - Costlow, John, 1958 July
    - Costlow, John, 1987 May
    - Costlow, John, 1986 May
    - Covery, Frank
    - Covi, Dr. Dario, 1970 June
    - Covington, Major, 1982 November
    - Cox, Jim, 1985 June
    - Cox, R. Merritt, 1967 August
    - Cox, Richard, 1983 February
    - Cox, Richard, 1972 July
    - Crapo, James, passport, 1985 September
    - Crapo, James, 1985 September
    - Craven, Braxton
    - Craven, President, Union Institute
    - Creasman, William, 1986 May
    - Creasman, William, 1974 November
    - Crenshaw, Dr. C., 1966 April
    - Crenshaw, Dr. James, Divinity, 1988 June
    - Crenshaw, Roy, 1959 January
    - Croft, Tom, 1983 April
    - Croft, Tom, 1981 January
    - Cromer, John A., 1976 May
    - Crotwell, Helen, 1979 March
    - Crotwell, Helen, 1977 August
    - Crowell, John F., 1947 March
    - Crowell, portrait, 1964 January
    - Culp, Jerome M., 1986 May
    - Cummings, 1958 April
    - Cummings, E. E., 1958 April
    - Cunningham, Glenn, 1968
    - Cushman, Dean and Divinity students in front of school, 1965 March
    - Cushman, Dean, vehicle, 1969 January
  - Faculty - D
    - Dakermandji, Farid, fellow, 1977 July
    - Daniel, Jim, 1971 September
    - Daniels, G. Neil, 1967 June
    - Daniels, Josephus, 1934, 1936
    - Danner, Dick, law, 1980 April
    - Danner, Richard, 1982 February
    - Danser/Danzer, Jean
    - Danser/Danzer, Jean, 1984 April
    - D'Armi Tom, 1984 July
    - Darrow, Susan, 1978 May
    - Dart, Raymond and Edwyn Simons, 1985 January
    - Davies, Dave, 1978 June
    - Davies, Dave, economics, 1976
    - Davies, David G., 1970 May
    - Davies, David, 1966 July
    - Davies, W. D., 1979 March
    - Davies, W. D., 1981 September
    - Davis, Divinity, 1960
    - Davison, Dr. and student with part of Trent Collection, 1957 October
    - Davison, Dr., portrait, 1970 September
    - Davison, Dr., and Carl, 1970 October
    - Davison, Dr. Wilbur, 1973 March
    - Davison, W.C., 1961
    - Davison with 2 medical students
    - Davison, front of magazine cover, 1962
    - Davison portrait, 1947 August 8
    - Davison at airline counter
    - Davison, Wilbur, 1961
    - Davison, 1959 May
    - Davison and medical school composite, 1957 January
    - Davison's coat and office, 1960 January
    - Davison, Dean W. C., 1939
    - Davison with medical students, 1952 December
    - Davison, 1960 May
    - Davison, as a young man, 1957 January
    - Davison and Chinese kids
    - Davison, Dean and Mrs. Morgan, 1954
    - Davison, information, 1961
    - Day, Dr. Eugene, 1962
    - Dealessi, L., 1963 May
    - Dean, Alfred, 1966 February
    - Deans Brinkley, Ball, Huckabee, 1963 March
    - DeBaies, Walter, 1976
    - Decker, Peter, 1979 April
    - Dees, Dr., 1961
    - Degrauelles, 1958 January
    - Delaney, Charles, 1964 July
    - Dellinger, David, business admn., 1970
    - Dellinger, Walter, law, 1971
    - Demaria, 1978 September
    - DeMott, Deborah, 1985 May
    - DeMott, Debra, law, 1976 March
    - DeNeef, 1970 June
    - Desrosier, Norman, glee club, 1956 February
    - Detomo, Paul M., purchasing, 1967 December
    - Deubner, David, 1985 February
    - Diamond, Irving, 1962 June
    - Dibone, 1978 September
    - Dickens, Robert, management sciences, 1977 July 25
    - Dickens, Robert, 1973 October
    - Dickens, Robert, 1966 December
    - Dickerson, Daniel, student, 1981 September
    - Dillard, Sandra Dean, 1967 May
    - Dirlik, Arif, 1976 April
    - Divinity School faculty, 1961 October
    - Dix, William P., 1979 October
    - Djordjevic, Dr. Milan, visiting professor, 1964 October
    - Douthat/Douthit, James, 1976 May
    - Douthat/Douthit, James, 1975 May
    - Douthat/Douthit, 1972 July
    - Dow, Neal, 1958 October
    - Dowell, Earl H., engineering dean, 1983 April
    - Dozeman, Alvin, 1962 May
    - Dresden, 1959 March
    - Dudley, Martha, 1973 October
    - Duffy/Duffey, Bernard, 1963 September
    - Duffy/Duffey, Bernard, 1982 February
    - Duffy, John, guest composer, 1965 January
    - Duncan, Pam, 1983 February
    - Dunkleman, Tom, passport, geology, 1984 March
    - Dunning, Jane, 1980 July
    - Dupree, 1985 September
    - Durden, Bob, 1977 February
    - Durden, Bob, 1975 December
    - Durden, Mrs. Bob, 1977 February
    - Durden, Bob and South Atlantic Quarterly, 1961
    - Durden, Bob, 1975 April
    - Durden, Bob, 1958 October
    - Dutrow, George, 1985 February
    - Dutrow, George, 1977 March
    - Dutton, Col. John, 1977 November
    - Dvorak, J., 1967 October
    - Dyer, Allen, 1976 January
  - Faculty - E
    - Eagle, Dr. and cat, 1962 November
    - Eaker, Mark, 1977 January
    - Easler, Martha, 1978 February
    - Eaton, May, 1967 August
    - Eddy, David
    - Edeburn, Judson, 1978 August
    - Edens, portrait made 1956 June
    - Efird, James, 1972 June
    - Efird, James, 1963 June
    - Egerton, Dr. Frank, 1981 July
    - Eichhoff, Darrell, visiting, 1976 February
    - Elchlepp, Dr., in office, 1966 October
    - Eldridge, A. F., AFROTC, 1976 August
    - Eldridge, Albert, passport, 1978 April
    - El Naga, Sayed, dining halls, 1976 September
    - Emory, Frank, 1978 September
    - Erickson, Harold
    - Ervin, Warren, passport, 1979 August 30
    - Estes, Dr. E. Harvey, Jr., 1974 January
    - Ethridge, 1978 April
    - Europe?, Dean Walter, 1976 May
    - Everett, Dr., 1962 February
    - Everett, Dr. John W., 1963 February
    - Everett, Dr. John W., anatomy, 1973 July
    - Everett, Robert R., engineering alumni, 1978 March
    - Everett, R. O., 1974 March
    - Evers, Mark, 1975 July
  - Faculty - F
    - Faculty member, Islamic and Asian Studies, 1978
    - Faculty, Retired, luncheon, 1967 March
    - Faculty Dinner: Alice Baldwin, President Few, Mrs. Hagen Smith, 1940
    - Faculty Members at Commencement
    - Faculty at ease, 1937
    - Faculty party, 1939
    - Fairbanks, Henry A., 1963 January
    - Faksh, Mahud A., 1982 July 1
    - Fant, Clyde, Divinity, 1984 June
    - Farris, Don M., 1956 January
    - Fasser, Carl, 1969 December
    - Feather, Dr. Bernard
    - Feezor, Allen D., 1971 June
    - Feezor, Allen, 1970 September
    - Fein, John, 1963 March
    - Fein, John, 1985 December
    - Feing, John, 1985 November
    - Fenner, Douglas, 1983 April
    - Fenner, Douglas, 1982 October
    - Fergerson, A. B., 1971 May
    - Fergerson, Dr. and group, 1964 July
    - Ferguson, Oliver, 1984 August
    - Ferree, Nancy, 1985 May
    - Ferster, passports
    - Few, President, 1978 November
    - Few, President and sons, 1966 August
    - Few, President, 1968 March
    - Fielding, Sarah, 1975
    - First, Joan, 1967 April
    - Fish, Don, geology passport, 1986 September
    - Fish, Dr., 1979 January
    - Fish, Peter, 1985 May
    - Fish, Stanley, 1986 May
    - Fisher, Al, 1981 April
    - Fleagle, 1980 January
    - Fleishman, Joel, 1981
    - Fleishman, Joel, 1976 January
    - Fleishman, Joel, passport
    - Fleishman, Joel, 1971 March
    - Flint, 1963
    - Flowers, Ann, 1974
    - Flowers, Anne, 1977 February
    - Flowers, portrait presentation, 1955 October
    - Flowers, Dr. and Henry R. Luce, convocation, 1940
    - Flowers, Maxine, 1971
    - Floyd at work, 1958 December
    - Fluke, Donald J., 1965 September
    - Forbes portrait, 1960
    - Forbus, B., F. Ross Porter, 1949 November 29
    - Forbus, Dr., 1964 August
    - Forbus, Wiley, 1959
    - Forbus, Dr. Wiley, 5000th autopsy, 1947 April 25
    - Forsyth, John, 1980 August
    - Forsyth, John, 1979 December
    - Foster, Benjamin, 1986 January
    - Foster, Elizabeth, passport, 1982 May
    - Fox, Richard G., 1973 April
    - France, Randell, 1975 November
    - Fraser-Reid, Bert, 1984 March
    - Freeman, Dr. Walter, with Dr. RS Crispell and Dr. Robert Graves, 1941 March 29
    - Fridovich, Irvin, 1960 April
    - Fridovich, Irwin, 1976 April
    - Friedberg, Ruth, 1987 February
    - Friedl, Ernestine, 1979 July
    - Friedl, Ernestine, 1983 January
    - Friedl, E., 1976 July
    - Freidlin, Joan, 1980 August
    - Freidrick, John, 1978 June
    - Fulkerson, Mary, 1983 July
    - Fuller, J. Peyton, 1970 March
    - Funderburk, Laney, passport, 1983 May
    - Funderburk, Laney, passport, 1985 January
    - Funderburk, Lois, passport, 1985 February
    - Funderburk trip, 1985 January
    - Furlow, John, 1977 September
  - Faculty - G
    - Galbraith, 1964 September
    - Gallagher, John, 1983 September
    - Gallemore, John, 1971 July
    - Gallie, Tom M.
    - Garber, Marcy, 1979 March
    - Garcia, Bael, 1967 July
    - Gardner, Grant, 1980 October
    - Garg, Devendra, engineering, 1985 April
    - Garg, Devendra, 1979 March
    - Garg, DP
    - Gaskell, Diana and patient, physical therapy, 1967 September
    - Gehman, Ila H., 1963 August
    - Gehman, W. Scott, 1956 September
    - Gelbert, Daniel H., forestry, 1977 March
    - Georgiade, Nicholas, 1969 May
    - Gerber, G., 1963 August
    - Gereffi, Gary, 1982
    - Germain, Claire, 1983 April
    - Germain, Claire, 1980 April
    - Ghosh, Sib, 1984 September [see also Gosh, Sib]
    - Gianinni, Gail
    - Gibbons, JP, portrait presentation to Dr. Busse, 1965 January
    - Gibson, Margaret, 1973 December
    - Gilchrist, Roy
    - Giraldo, Z. I., 1979 March 8
    - Githens, 1959 June
    - Goffen, Rona, 1980 April
    - Golding, Martin, 1985 May
    - Goldner with patient, 1963 October
    - Goldner, 1963 October
    - Goldner, Dr. Leonard, 1965 May
    - Garcia-Gomez, Miguel, 1982 April
    - Gomez, M. G., 1975
    - Gomez, M. G., with paper, 1975
    - Goodling, Richard, 1965 September
    - Goodman, William, 1965 September
    - Goodrich, Dr. J. K., 1970 May
    - Goodson, Bishop, 1980 September
    - Goodwin, Crawford/Craufurd, 1966 June
    - Goodwin, Crawford/Craufurd, 1983 October
    - Goodwin, Crawford/Craufurd, 1970 October
    - Goodwin, Mrs., passport
    - Goodwyn, Lawrence C., history, 1977 March
    - Gordy, Dr. Walter, 1985 September
  - Faculty - G (cont'd) (Box 33)
    - Goree, John A., 1963 March
    - Gosh, Sib, passport, 1986 May
    - Gosling, Bill, 1983 November
    - Gossett, Glenn, dining halls, 1985 August
    - Grabowski, Henry G., economics, 1977 March
    - Graham, 1963 December
    - Graham, Doyle, 1987 June
    - Grant, 1963 March
    - Green, Bill, 1985 September
    - Green, William, 1980 July
    - Green, Bill, visa photos, 1973 October
    - Green, 1961 May
    - Green, Bill, passport, 1979 October
    - Green, William
    - Green, Bill, 1970 September
    - Green, Mrs. William, passport, 1983 September
    - Greenberg
    - Greenfield, Joe, 1987 September
    - Greg, Bob, 1979 March
    - Gregg, John R.
    - Gresov, Chris, Fuqua, 1987 September
    - Griffith, Bill, 1983 March
    - Griffith, Dean and wife, passports, dean of student affairs, 1977 March
    - Griffiths and Terry Sanford, 1983 October
    - Griffiths, Phillip, provost, 1985 September
    - Griffiths, Phillip A., provost, passport, 1984 May
    - Grisom, Dr. in lab, 1963 May
    - Gross, Dr., dinner honoring, 1959 May
    - Grossman, Dave, football trainer, 1978 August
    - Grueling, Mrs., 1978 November
    - Grzbowski, K., passport, 1969 April
    - Grzbowski, K., 1969 April
    - Grzbowski, Mrs., passport, 1969 April
  - Faculty - H
    - Haas, William, purchasing, 1967 November
    - Haas, William, 1980 May
    - Hackel, Don B., 1962 November
    - Hacker, Herbert, 1979 November
    - Hacker, H., 1965
    - Hade, Dr. Kirby, research grant, 1965 July
    - Hall, Hugh, 1977 August
    - Hall, Joanne, 1980 June
    - Hall, Kenneth
    - Hamil, Wink, 1981 June
    - Hamlin
    - Hamill, R. W., III, manager, real estate investments, 1981
    - Hammond, Sam, 1978 May
    - Hammond, Sam, 1983 May
    - Hammond, Dr., lab, 1967 November
    - Hammond, W. E., 1969
    - Hammond, Dr. William, 1980 September
    - Handler, Dr., 1967 February
    - Hanks, John, passport, 1972 March
    - Hanks, John, passport, 1985 June
    - Hanks, John, 1987 February
    - Hanks, John, 1980 November
    - Hanson, John, 1982 June
    - Hanks, Nancy, 1985 July
    - Hanks, Mrs., passport, 1981 March
    - Hanks, Nancy, 1983 September
    - Hannenburg, Bill, 1978 February
    - Harmon, Charlie, 1981 April
    - Harmon, Charles, 1975 September
    - Harrar, Dean and Fred White, 1967 August
    - Harris, B. and B. Foster, announcer, basketball coach, 1977 December
    - Harris, Fletcher, 1974 April
    - Harris, Gina
    - Harris, Dr. Jerome, 1961 May
    - Harris, Dr. and Drs. Howell and Louis Diamond
    - Hart, Dr. Deryl, 1955 February
    - Hart and Knight, 1964 May
    - Hart, Dr., receiving award, 1955 March
    - Hart portrait presentation and dinner at Hope Valley Club, 1955 October
    - Hart, Dr. and Visiting doctors, 1957 June
    - Hart, Deryl feature, 1960 May
    - Hart and Edens, 1960 June
    - Hart, Dr., receiving a check from Hamble Oil, 1963 January
    - Hart, Dr. presenting check to Prof. Billings
    - Hart, Dr., receiving check from Standard Oil, 1963 January
    - Hart, President receiving check from Sears Foundation by Mr. Patton, 1963 January
    - Hart, Dr., birthday party for, 1963 July
    - Hart, Dr. and Dr. Knight, press conference, 1963 September
    - Harting, Gerald, 1976 February
    - Harward, Steve, 1965 September
    - Harward, Steve, 1977 November 3
    - Harwell, G. C., 1963 May
    - Haskins, Marye, passport, 1969 November
    - Hasham, C. L., 1975 March
    - Hatsell, 1970
    - Haupht, Dale, football coach, 1978 February
    - Haupt, Jeff, 1982 April
    - Hauser, Charles Roy, 1979 March
    - Havely, Bob, 1981 November
    - Havighurst, 1965 July
    - Havighurst, Clark C., 1973 November
    - Havighurst, Clark C., law, 1976 April
    - Havighurst, Dr., 1979 August
    - Havighurst, Clark, 1984 May
    - Havrilesky, Tom, 1984 May
    - Hawley, Willis, 1979
    - Hayes, Brenda, 1985 November
    - Hayes, Captain Morris L., 1975 August
    - Hayes, Captain Morris L., NROTC, 1977
    - Hayes, Richard, 1971 October
    - Hayes, R. B., 1969 December
    - Hayes, Vita, 1975 July
    - Heilman, Elizabeth, 1979 December
    - Hellmers, Henry, 1981 May
    - Hellmers, Dr. and Mrs., passport, 1981 May
    - Hellmers, Henry, 1972
    - Henderson, James, business manager, 1976 October
    - Hendicks, Paul, 1981 July
    - Henkens, Robert, 1969 January
    - Henricksen and Haywood at Christmas dinner with Knight, 1966 December
    - Henry, J., 1964
    - Henry, Stuart, passport, 1975 April
    - Henry, Stuart, 1979 April
    - Henson, Tom, glassblower
    - Herbert, George, 1978 April
    - Herlinger, John, 1977 September
    - Heron, Duncan, 1960 May
    - Heron, Duncan, 1976 January
    - Herring, Dean, retirement dinner with Jones, Jordan and Thigpen, 1965 March
    - Herzog, Dr.
    - Herzog, Fredrick, 1969 May
    - Heyden, Dr. S., 1968 January
    - Heyman, Albert, 1963 May
    - Heyman, Dr., 1973 May
    - Hickman and Harris, 1957 July
    - High, S., 1961
    - Hill, Robert, music, 1988 November
    - Hine, Dr. Frederick, 1961 May
    - Hines, Debbie, geology passport, 1985 April
    - Hobbs, Bob, drama, 1987 May
    - Hobbs, Bob, drama, 1988 July
    - Hobbs, Marcus, 1978 April
    - Hodel, Richard E.
    - Hodges, Luther Jr., 1979 January 15
    - Hogue, Carol, Hanes House, 1983 February
    - Hohman, Dr. portrait presentation, 1964 October
    - Holland, Clyde, passport
    - Holleman, nursing, 1973 March
    - Holley, Bill, 1969 January
    - Holley, I. B. and books, 1964 October
    - Holley, I. B., uniform, 1975 December
    - Holman, retired faculty, 1961
    - Holsti, Ole, 1983 February
    - Holsti, Ole, 1977 October
    - Honea, Sherry, Highland Hospital, 1975 July
    - Hopkins, E. and wife, passports
    - Horowitz, Donald, 1985 May
    - Horowitz, Donald, 1984 August
    - Houpt, Corinne, 1982 February
    - Hostetter, Mike
    - Howard, E. J., volleyball coach, 1978 April
    - Howard, Emma Jean, 1974
    - Howard, J. W., political science, 1963 April
    - Howard, W. K.
    - Howell and Harris in lab, 1957 July
    - Hough, Jerry, 1979 September
    - Hoyler, Hamilton M., 1964 July
    - Hubbell, J. B., 1978 January
    - Hubbell, J. B., 1978 July
    - Huber, Tom, 1980 April
    - Hudson, Fitzgerald S., engineering alumni, 1978 March
    - Hudson, William R., 1961 August 16
    - Huestis, Mrs., 1978 April
    - Huestis, Mrs., passport
    - Huestis on the mountain, 1975 November
    - Huestis, Mr., 1979 January
    - Huestis, Charles, 1983 July
    - Hull, Julia, 1978 January
    - Hull, Sam, passport, 1985 March
    - Hurlburt, Allen S., 1971 November
    - Huse, 1961 May
    - Husing, Ted, Woman's Auditorium reception, CBS sports broadcaster, 1946 April 22
    - Huston, Sam R., 1971
    - Hylander, Bill, 1984 June
    - Hylander, Dr. William, 1980 September
  - Faculty - I
    - Ingram, O. Kelly, 1967 January
    - Ingram, Mrs., formerly Carol Cox, 1963 April
    - Ingram, 1976 October
    - Innis, Cathy, women's field hockey, 1978 April
  - Faculty - J
    - Jackson, Dr. J. J., 1971 February
    - Jackson, Richard L., 1973 February
    - Jacobs, Merle E., 1959 May
    - Jaeger, Jon, 1972 August
    - James, Robert, composer of Duke Alma Mater with new tennis coach)
    - Janocrat, A., 1963 August
    - Jayne, Ben, 1984 July
    - Jayne, Benjamin, forestry, 1977 March
    - Jedierowski, Jim, 1984 August
    - Jeffrey, Dr., 1971 May